(Bernadette:)I went to Catholic school!
(Howard:)Okay, well, it's getting late.
(Howard:)This was terrific.
(Howard:)You win.
(Howard:)Bernie?
(Leonard:)I think the word you're
looking for is "befuddled."
(Sheldon:)My catapult flings my bishop
(Sheldon:)to Howard's Queen's Gorilla two.
(Penny:)Nice.
(Howard:)Okay, rook to transporter pad.
(Howard:)And he comes out at...
(Howard:)...Leonard's Queen's Bishop
five-and-a-third.
Check on Leonard.
(Amy:)Hang on.
(Leonard:)When is my pawn allowed
to use the golf cart?
(Sheldon:)When it's done charging.
(Sheldon:)Or you land on
the time machine.
(Bernadette:)Obviously.
(Leonard:)Oh, oh...
(Leonard:)Beekeeper to King 12.
(Leonard:)I capture your pope
and release the swarm.
(Leonard:)Checkmate on Sheldon.
I knew I should've given
my pope the jet pack.
(Raj(still naked):)Hey, I've got winners.